Tyrant. Liar. Racist. A hole in one.
Fahrenheit 11/9 is a documentary film directed by Michael Moore.
Michael Moore's provocative documentary explores the two most important
questions of the Trump Era: How did we get here, and how do we get out.
Self, played by Michael Moore.
Self, played by Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez.
Self, played by Bernie Sanders.
Self, played by David Hogg.
Self (archive footage), played by Donald Trump.
Self, played by Steve Bannon.
Fahrenheit 11/9 is a 2018 American documentary by filmmaker Michael Moore about the 2016 United States
presidential election and first presidency of Donald Trump up to the time of the film's release.
The film is a follow-up to Moore's Fahrenheit 9/11 (2004), a
documentary about the presidency of George W.
The film had its world premiere on September 6, 2018, at the 2018 Toronto International Film Festival,
and was released in the United States on September 21, 2018, by Briarcliff Entertainment.
Despite grossing $6.7 million worldwide, one of the lowest totals of Moore's career,
Fahrenheit 11/9 received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film received a nomination for Best Documentary
Screenplay from the Writers Guild of America.
Three people depicted in the film (Donald and Melania Trump and Kellyanne Conway) collectively received four
nominations at the 39th Golden Raspberry Awards and won three, including Worst Actor for Donald Trump.
The film explores themes of usa president,
billionaire, flint michigan, school shooting.